Hello everyone! I'm Rei Oizono from Sakurazaka46!
I'm at a hair salon right now!
I've come to the salon to get a haircut!
Now, I would like to cut my hair!
I would like to cut it!
Oh!
Now, I'm going to touch my hands...
Here we go!
♪ BGM
♪ Chime
♪ Chime ♪
♪ Chime, chime, chime ♪
What?
Oh, I'm so nervous!
I'm nervous!
I'm nervous.
Oh, here it comes.
Woooo!
I found a toy for you.
Oh!
Isn't it nice?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Then, I'd like to continue.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's gone!
Surprisingly, you didn't get it.
That's for sure.
I'll hang up now.
Yes, please.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
I'll go.
He's not here.
Yes, hey Jana.
Jana's soccer.
Hi.
I'm off.
Ah, parenting.
Earthquake in Kerbic
Is there a lot of free stuff?
Do you get a lot of free stuff?
Do I get a lot of free stuff?
Maybe not yet.
I'll tell you why I hate it this time.
I've been a black lone since the animated movie.
I've been a Lorne with black hair since the animated movie.
I'm Lorne and I'm Lonz.
I think there's an image of me as Lon's.
Well, in the year 2020
I wanted to be a new me.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
I was wondering if it would be okay if I had a short period of time
I thought it would be good to have a short period of time
I decided to come.
What about the members' mission?
It was supposed to be a secret, but they sent me the schedule.
But then you sent it to me in a way that everyone could see it.
But when you sent it to me in a way that everyone could see it, they found out... and that's when the tension started.
You're going to cut your hair? I was so surprised.
And when I got it and told him I was going to cut it...
I said, "I'm going to cut it!" And they were so excited.
I'm so glad you're looking forward to it.
And Lisa asked me again if I thought she'd look good in short hair.
But maybe I've already asked her the way people want me to ask them. She said she thought it would look good on me every time.
You're so kind.
That's great.
I wonder if there really are a lot of them here.
What was it?
The Hamix of Tenryu Gardens.
Marion.
The one that was on the computer at Hamik's.
vomit vomit vomit
looks like
I don't have a problem if an amateur is on the screen.
Oh my God, this screen.
the whole thing is like 10 minutes long?
The video
If you like the video, please give it a high rating.
It's been a long time, right?
Thanks to number 5, I got some rest.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I really took the day off.
I'm really sorry about today.
I'm sorry.
wh
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
ní may not be
Afternoon
You're so smooth.
LOL.
I'm so self-treated.
After the treatment.
In the bath
comb through it in the bath
comb it out in the bath before rinsing it off.
What?
Is that okay?
Do you comb it after shampooing?
After shampooing?
What's the point?
It doesn't make sense.
She said it doesn't mean anything.
I tried to tell him, but he said it didn't make sense.
Anyway, does it make sense to unscrew something with your mouth?
It does make sense.
What? Shuffling must mean something too.
Rina Matsuda once gave me a large tartament from a place called Oshima as a birthday present.
I loved Oshima. It looked very silky.
Also, Ryo-san recommended it to me, and you used it a lot.
I would leave the tare treatments at a place called Waikartz.
I used to do it the day before a live concert, before a beagly, before recording a movie, and so on.
So next time you shoot a plastic, I'll be short.
Have you thought of Lisa's tips?
Short.
Which means.
The next eight singles.
Like the reagle.
Or Real Monicles.
What's going to meet
I'll take my time over there.
I'll show you.
You've always had straight black hair.
Backwards.
I'll show you.
I've had people tell me they're looking for a haircut.
Next time, please do your best to find it.
Just a little camera.
How old are you?
I've been in elementary school for a long time.
Yesterday... no, middle school was short.
I was short in high school, too.
I was in high school, too.
That's why middle school was so long...
4 years?
9 years?
No, I grew it for about 5 years.
It looks like I'm in the middle of a process, doesn't it?
Ta-da! This is what it looks like!
A little more.
You see, it looks like you're falling down.
Oh, oh, I see it again!
That's great.
Good, good, good.
I'll have to send you a picture of Sen-chan.
She sent me a picture just now.
Yummy.
I think everyone knew about it yesterday.
Everyone knew about it from Noru's call yesterday.
Tenchan was the only one who asked.
That's just like Ten-chan!
Is this really Bob?
Is it Bob? Of course it's Bob.
It's fine. I mean, my hair grows fast, so it's fine.
Don't worry about it. I'll leave it to you.
Ooh!
Huh?
What do you think?
Personally, I'm very satisfied.
I'm so happy!
This, this, this.
This is one of them, isn't it?
This is also possible, isn't it?
This is also an option.
Yes, it is!
It's an ant!
Yay! It's done!
Please fit as many as you can!
Please put on a lot of long hair, too.
Is it this tight?
It's too tight! Can I wait a bit to see it?
Nyoo...
Wait, that's a little scary.
Look, it's a little scary.
All of this.
Is it a little creepy?
Let me show you something.
It's like this.
Oh, my God.
Thank you... for everything.
And voila! It's done!
Oh! It looks like this!
It's done! I am personally very satisfied with the image this time!
I think it was a great success!
I think some of you may not be familiar with it yet.
I would be very happy if you could give me lots of compliments in the comments!
If you think the bob looks good on me, please leave a comment.
If you think the bob looks good on me, please give me a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to my channel!
I'm looking forward to working hard again with a new haircut!
Thank you very much for watching my video!
See you soon!